

ESMOND AGHAROVBOKHAN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

I am a software developer who have gained several knowledge and experience in recent times. I have been working for more than one year now as a software developer with experience and skills in several web technologies that help create powerful, userfriendly websites. In the past, i have amassed plethora of skills in various web technologies such as, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, ReactJS and many more. I have also successfully developed a gas ordering systems application by putting the aforementioned skills into use. I have collaborated with others to work on project relating to web which makes me not only target driven, but also a team player.

PHONE: +234 7035967785

EMAIL:

esmondagha@gmail.com

GITHUB:

https://github.com/Esmondsmith/gas

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF KYRENIA – Northern Cyprus

2019 – 2021. **MBA.**

DELTA STATE UNIVERSITY - Nigeria

2010 – 2014. **B.SC, ECONOMICS.**

WORK EXPERIENCE

MOAT ACADEMY FOR DEVELOPERS - Software Dev.

2023 May – Present, **Nigeria**.

- Software development
- Database administration
- Collaborative projects

DANEHI ENTERPRISE - Project Supervisor

2022 – 2023, **Nigeria**.

- Evaluate performance and provide feedback
- Planning and implementing decisions

UNION BANK PLC - Marketer

2017 – 2018, **Nigeria**.

- Completed in-depth review of market conditions and customer preferences
- Developed marketing strategies for clients
- Identified appropriate marketing channels and target customers for campaigns

HOBBIES SKILLS Board games (Scrabble & Chess) •HTML5 •React.js •PHP •jQuery •JavaScript •Bootstrap (Framework) •Tailwind CSS, •Cascading Style swimming Sheets (CSS) • SQL • Git and GitHub Outdoor activities cooking **PROJECT MANAGEMENT & TRACKING TOOLS** Computers 1. Jira 2. Slack 3. Trello **REFERENCES** Available upon request.